[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "You're quite fascinating, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Thanks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joaquin"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "How do you reinforce the kind of story that you guys can tell America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, it means that there's this -- as Joaquin has said many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, what I think is that when folks compare where the nation was when President Obama took office and you heard several speakers say that, losing 750,000 to 800,000 jobs a month and then you compare where we are now, 29 straight months of private sector job growth, 4.5 million new jobs, that I'm confident he's going to lay out the case very convincingly for why even though we haven't made the -- we're not where we want to be, we have made significant progress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 165, "question": "How fired up are you about this election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "RP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I am incensed --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", ":", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "What do you think of the way they've been going at each other and the issues that are likely to be the determining issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I think the most exciting -- may be exciting for me because I'm over here on the left.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Are you voting for the party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I don't think as a party they have a clear directive anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Do you think that the dream that you grew up with has changed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, yes, probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "The whole thing about Pussy Riots in Russia was ridiculous, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Of course it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Then the traditional singer goes off and, you know, wants to be the new Michael Jackson, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes, I had to find a vehicle big enough for my ego.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "What was it like the second time around to get back with the group and do your thing again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, you know, we were because I think in the middle of the solo records we did the greatest hits.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "He wears those -- like all he wears is like the jogging suits, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Hey, how can I help you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Well, I have a guitar here for you to take a look at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Where in the world did you get this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I got this from my father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Is it because, in fact, ironically, America is suffering economically and when that happens, a business like yours tends to do well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "That's sort of a misnomer.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "I mean who comes in your store?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "It's everybody, especially our store.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "I know there must be a lot of surprises, but when you look back, what have been the moments you go, wow, when somebody's brought something in that's really knocked your socks off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "That happens actually a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "This is actually the battle plan for Iwo Jima, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iwo Jima"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Who brought this in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "It was a person, his father had been on Iwo Jima.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "How do you assess a value?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$3,500"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Would you remember even the ballpark?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I think is it was right around $3,500, something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "So 8 grand, it's coming off the wall right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Eight thousand dollars or an Iwo Jima plan, I'll take the 8 grand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2000"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "So, do you remember his story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Yes, I -- I think his story was basically that he, you know, he got injured, wasn't able to compete in 2000 and was doing some other things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "ORGAN: So do you remember his story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What were they -- how do you quantify an Olympic medal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "That's a very difficult thing, because they rarely if ever get on the market.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Do you remember what you paid him for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Actually, I gave him a loan on them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "So he'll never get them back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Sad, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "It's sad but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Do you ever feel sad, or is the lesson you hand down to your son, you can't afford to get emotionally involved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "One of the things is a pawn broker with a heart is usually a pawn broker out of business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Is there anything you would turn down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Yeah --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "ORGAN: Have you ever turned anything down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "We won't take any German World War II items.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I won't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Is there any other sort of thing you feel strongly you wouldn't want to be party to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I mean, just anything in that area.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "And I suppose the obvious question is what is the most expensive thing that you've ever bought?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "It's a real easy one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Do people actually walk in with gold bars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Oh, yeah, every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Tell us the biggest -- what's the biggest chunk of gold you've ever had to deal with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I can't remember what it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Five hundred thousand dollars, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What is the -- if you're smart, what is the markup if you move quickly on something like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "In our shop, it's weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "So on that kind of thing, that huge amount of gold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "One percent I'm happy with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I mean, it's a lot of people don't understand we're in business, would say, I would never do that for one percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Take the cash when you can?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yeah, you have to -- I mean, it's business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I'm very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 527, "question": "How are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I'm disappointed actually because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I've just imagined I would meet the rebellious, explosive, spitfire, the angry young woman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "You are, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Respectful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "You can vote in the American election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "I can indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Have you voted before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I have voted long distance as I traveled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RBR", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "What is your leaning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "My meaning is towards the spiritual activism, less the political one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "When you travel around the world as you do, usually successfully, what impression do you get about America these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, I can share mine and then others.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What is Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "The Britain are the thoughtful, intellectual --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Handsome?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I dare say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Have you detected it changing in the last few years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I -- upon chatting with a lot of people around the planet, I think a lot of people are -- perceive America to be a little narcissistic and a little traumatized.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "You're into this attachment parenting, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Your son is two now, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Almost.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Do you mind me asking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yeah, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Are you still breast feeding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Are you heading into the four or five-year-old breastfeeding possibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "I live in the present moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Now, how has marriage and parenting calmed you down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I would say I'm less reactive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "What's the most passionate when you've written a song ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "I think anger can move worlds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "What was the song you wrote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Just this morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "When you look back, can you remember writing a big song that was just driven out sheer, blind fury?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Yeah, reflecting on ex-boyfriends can bring that out in any woman I think, or any man, frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Who gets to say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "We're also unfortunately have to get around to talking about music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "What's that all about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "It wasn't in real time, so it was super disconcerting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "If I said to you when you were a young Alanis in Canada, you're going to end up married to a rapper called Mario Soul Eye Treadway, and have a son called Ever, would you have believed me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "I would have said thank Christ; can I skip over all the hard part and wait for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mario Soul Eye Treadway"], "LOCATION": ["Canada"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Is this true love for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "So in love is a little bit of a tough term for me What does that even mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Where your heart either aches or breaks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "So you're just a incurable romantic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "I was a love addict through and through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["P.M. Melody"]}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Were you drawn to constantly inappropriate men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "I was drawn to the back walking away, as the beautiful P.M. Melody (ph) would say in her book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "How did you know this guy was for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Values being the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "Do you pray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "I pray all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "The interview to end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Whereas the answer is probably compromise I would guess, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "I don't know if compromise is actually the word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120907pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Do you like being a celebrity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]